Week 10. Day 1. Man or machine. The strange new world of e-skin.
Limb. Flexible. Sensor. Heart rate. Enable. Surgery.
Handheld. Gadget. Appear. Day 2. Bats and bees are dying.
Sting. Pollinate. Productive. Threaten. Pest. Mosquito.
Colony. Collapse. Phenomenon. Pesticide. Malnutrition. Genetically. Modify. Fungus.
Cuddly. Day 3. Music and mood. Soothe. Savage. Beat. Dopamine. Slightly. Addictive. Pulse.
Rate. Chill. Participant. Inject. Be flooded with. Collector. Day 4. Dr. Bronner soaps.
A variety of. Run. Profit. Executive. Five times. The amount of. Minimize. Certified.
Unite. Sum up. Capitalism. Typical. Charitable. Day 5. Body language across cultures. Frown.
Movement. Cheek. Shocking. Pat. Unacceptable. Soul. From time to time.
Communication. Day 6. Greek theater and Dionysus. Theater. Dionysus.
Blockbuster. Be traced back to. Fertility. Worship. Mythical. Center. Chorus. Ensemble.
Priest. Tragedy. Comedy. Prologue. Performance. Blow up. Worshiper. Whisper.